Interviewer: What animal would you most like to see in the wild,
for example, on a safari?
Hope: Oh, that’s a really good question.
Probably an elephant.
Interviewer: Why?
Hope: I think they’re amazing.
They’re so big, and just, they sort of live in the wilderness, and yeah.
Interviewer: Do you have a phobia?
Mairi: I’m frightened of spiders.
Interviewer: How long have you had it?
Mairi: Er, since I was about five or six I think, but I’m not sure.
Interviewer: How does it affect your life?
Mairi: Um, I normally have to check a room to see if there’s a big spider in it
before I go to sleep, because, one time a spider, er, joined me in my bed.
Interviewer: Who’s the oldest person you know well?
Dave: My great aunt is a hundred and four, living in California.
Interviewer: What kind of life has she had?
Dave: She has had a great life.
She’s still travelling at a hundred and four.
Interviewer: Do you do any sport or exercise?
Sarah: I run and I hike, and I do yoga.
Interviewer: Do you enjoy it?
Sarah: I love hiking, hiking is my favourite,
and I just love being in nature and outdoors,
and experiencing nature on foot.
Interviewer: Are you a morning or evening person?
Kathy: Um, I’m a morning person.
Um, I feel a lot more awake in the morning than in the evening, um,
so I tend to get up early, even when I’m not at, even when I’m not at work.
Um, and I prefer to go to bed earlier.